rapidload.com 2016-03-11

# RapidLoad | Privacy Policy

RapidLoad, an executable program together with the entire contents of our documentation and software package (the “Product”) belonging to OR Interactive Ltd., (the "Company") takes your privacy very seriously. Please read the following to learn more about Company's Privacy Policy ("Policy"). This Policy details how Company receives, collects and uses information in connection with our website and Product provided on the www.rapidload.com website (the website and the Product collectively referred to herein as "Site").

### Collection and Use of Information

Company does not automatically collect any personally identifiable information, such as names, e-mail, age, gender, address, telephone numbers, login names and passwords or other self-identifying information ("Personal Information").

Company may use cookies on the Site. Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies make web-surfing easier by saving preferences and browsing patterns while you are on Company's Site. Cookies may be used to analyze Site usage, improve content, customize the Site's content and layout as well as for other customer service purposes. Company's use of cookies is in no way linked to any Personal Information.

Company may automatically receive and record certain non-personally identifiable information on its server logs from your browser, including your IP address, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), cookie information, and the webpage that a user visits. Company collects non-personally identifiable information for general purposes, including but not limited to analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking user movements, conducting research, and providing anonymous reporting to internal and external clients. Company will not link any Personal Information, including e-mail addresses, with aggregate data of its users.

### Sharing and Disclosure of Information

Company does not rent, sell, or share any information about the user with any third-parties. Company may disclose your Personal Information if Company believes such action is necessary to: (a) comply with the law or legal process served on Company (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Company (including the enforcement of our agreements);or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Company services or members of the public.

### Digital Millennium Copyright Act Notice

If you are a trademark owner or an agent of a trademark owner and believe that content available by means of RapidLoad's website or software publications infringes one or more of your trademarks, please immediately notify RapidLoad's Copyright Agent by means of emailed notice (dmca@rapidload.com) and include the information described above for DMCA notices. RapidLoad handles notices it receives of trademark violations via a process very similar to the DMCA Notice process that is described above for copyrights. In addition to the DMCA Notice requirements, RapidLoad requires that the entire Trademark Notice be made by the trademark owner (or her agent) under penalty of perjury.

### Children's Privacy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important to us. We operate our website in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). We never knowingly collect or maintain information at or on our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is directed at or structured to attract anyone under 13. Visitors younger than 13 years of age may NOT use the Company website and software and must LEAVE immediately.

### Explicit Content

You understand that by using the Service, you may encounter content that may be deemed offensive, indecent, or objectionable, which content may or may not be identified as having explicit language. Nevertheless, you agree to use the Site at your sole risk and that Company shall have no liability to you for content that may be found to be offensive, indecent, or objectionable. Company shall have no liability or responsibility to you for any content or materials that may be available in connection with the Site that you might find objectionable.

### Information collected during the install process

During installation process the Product may collect the following information: the name, id and the version number of the operating system running on the end user's computer, a list of programs and drivers installed on the user's computer together with their version numbers and a list of browsers installed on the user’s computer together with the version numbers and settings.

This information is anonymous and does not contain any personal information such as names and email addresses, and is collected solely for the purpose of ensuring that the product will work correctly on the end user's computer, offer any relevant third-party software that you might want during the installation process and creating an overall better end user experience.

### Security

Company takes reasonable precaution to protect Personal Information from misuse, loss and unauthorized access. Although Company cannot guarantee that Personal Information will not be subject to unauthorized access, Company has physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect the Personal Information. Personal Information is protected by secured networks and access is limited to a few authorized employees and personnel. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however.

### Changes to Policy

From time to time, Company may revise this Policy. Company will post the revised Policy on the Site, so that users can always be aware of what information Company collects, how the information is used and under what circumstances such information may be disclosed.

### Contact Information

Please direct all questions in connection with this Policy via e-mail to privacy@rapidload.com

 _Last modified September 15th 2013_
